The week 一週間 日曜日から土曜日までの名前
Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday
曜日の尋ね方
What day of the week is it today?
今日は何曜日ですか?
今一度
What day of the week is it today?
その返答
日曜日ですから土曜日ですまで
It's Sunday, it's Monday, it's Tuesday, it's Wednesday, it's Thursday, it's Friday, it's Saturday
次は一週間の曜日の順序
日曜日は一週間の第一日ですから
土曜日は一週間の第七日ですまで
Sunday is the first day of the week
Monday is the second day of the week
Tuesday is the third day of the week
Wednesday is the fourth day of the week
Thursday is the fifth day of the week
Friday is the sixth day of the week
Saturday is the seventh day of the week
順位を示す数字
第一から第三十まで
次に第十、第二十、第三十、第四十と十ずつ加えて
第一百まで数え進みます
70th, 80th, 90th, 100th
音に歌ひとつ
A nursery rhyme
Solomon Grande
Born on Monday, christened on Tuesday
Married on Wednesday
Took ill on Thursday
Worse on Friday
Died on Saturday
Buried on Sunday
This is the end of Solomon Grande